greatwesternbank.com 2002-12-03

# Privacy Policy

**Online Privacy Policy of Great Western Bank**

Great Western Bank recognizes the importance of the privacy of your personal information. Because of our interest in protecting our valued customers and others visiting our web site, we have developed the following principles and disclosures, continuing our commitment to provide outstanding service to Omaha and surrounding communities: 

**Use and Collection of Your Personal Information**

Great Western Bank collects and retains information through our online sites to assist us with communicating with you, responding to your questions, and tracking visitation to improve the efficiency of our site. We will NOT obtain information that identifies you personally unless you specifically choose to disclose such information. Great Western Bank will NOT sell personal information to a third party for the purpose of solicitation or for a third party's own independent use without prior notification and opportunity to decline. We may, however, share information if it is required by law (i.e. subpoena, investigation of fraudulent activity, etc.) or within the departments of the bank for the purpose of delivering products and services to you, including communication and customer service. 

**Employee Access and Use of Personal Information**

Great Western Bank's employees are committed to and are required to follow our Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy provides that all employees are required to keep all customer information confidential and never disclose this information inside or outside Great Western Bank unless they are conducting appropriate bank business. Access to personally identifiable information is limited to those with a business reason for knowing such information. 

**Protection of Information**

Great Western Bank has established security standards for access that provide for protection of personal information. These security standards include the requirement of access codes, firewalls and encryption, where deemed appropriate. 

**Privacy and E-Mail**

When you send us an e-mail, Great Western Bank will retain your e-mail address, the content of the e-mail, and our response to better serve you and assist us with any follow-up questions that you may have. Our e-mails are not secure; if the information that you are sending to us is of a confidential nature, please consider using the telephone, fax or mail. 

**Maintenance and Accuracy of Personal Information**

If you have any concerns about the accuracy of your personal information, you may contact us by e-mail, mail or by telephone at the phone number or address listed below. Any discrepancies will be corrected in a timely manner. Thank you for your interest in privacy and Great Western Bank! 

Great Western Bank  
P. O. Box 4070  
Omaha, NE 68104-0070  
(402) 551-4310 or (800) 952-2015  
E-Mail: [pcbank@radiks.net](mailto:pcbank@radiks.net)

**In Omaha phone: 1-402-551-4310, outside Omaha phone: 1-800-952-2039  
Email: [pcbank@greatwesternbank.com](mailto:pcbank@greatwesternbank.com)**

Deposits| Internet Banking |  Credit Cards  | Investments| Loans|  Current Rates  
Trust Services | XpressPhone Banking | Employment | Email   
Financial Calculators | Privacy Policy  | Online Accounts| [ MyCardStatement.com](http://www.mycardstatement.com/)  
 Newsletters| About Us |  Great Western Bank Home 

* * *

© 1996-2002 Great Western Bank  
Site Design: [ACTONet](http://www.acton.com/ACTONet)
